[
    {
        "question": "How much cash does the weapon `Assault Rifle` cost in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "$5,000",
            "$10,000",
            "$15,000",
            "$2,000"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Halloween 2018 event weapon in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "Bonecage",
            "Crossbow",
            "Military Axe",
            "Laser Pistol"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How much cash does the `Military Truck` cost in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "$30,000",
            "$20,000",
            "$5,000",
            "$15,000"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which gamepass grants you access to the `Railgun` in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "VIP",
            "Mega VIP",
            "Ultra VIP",
            "Elite VIP"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which gamepass grants you access to the `Railgun` in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "VIP",
            "Mega VIP",
            "Ultra VIP",
            "Elite VIP"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which vehicle is the most expensive in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "Helicopter",
            "Jeep",
            "Military Truck",
            "Armoured Carrier"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How many seasonal events have happened in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "2",
            "6",
            "7",
            "10"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two weapons do players spawn in with in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "Laser Pistol and Katana",
            "Handgun and Knife",
            "Railgun and Golden Pistol",
            "Luger Pistol and Knife"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ranks are in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "5",
            "7",
            "8",
            "2"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What reward do players get for reaching the `General` rank in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "Golden Pistol",
            "Golden Railgun",
            "Golden Luger",
            "Golden Katana"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What badge is rewarded to players who kill the creator in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "Loyal Soldier",
            "Elite Soldier",
            "General",
            "Epic Soldier"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What in-game reward do players receive for joining the Saikou group in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "Golden Katana",
            "Military Axe",
            "$2,500 starter cash",
            "$5,000 starter cash"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What in-game reward do players receive for reaching the rank `Colonel` in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "$500,000 starter cash + ingame overhead rank",
            "$500,000 starter cash",
            "$450,000 starter cash + ingame overhead rank",
            "$200,000 starter cash + ingame overhead rank"
        ],
        "answer": 1
	},
	{
        "question": "How many tycoons are featured within Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "7",
            "6",
            "8"
        ],
        "answer": 3
	},
	{
        "question": "Which weapon is not included within the VIP gamepass?",
        "options": [
            "Jetpack",
            "Auto Sniper",
            "Jetpack",
            "Anti tank vehicle"
        ],
        "answer": 2
	},
	{
        "question": "How many vehicles are in Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "7",
            "5",
            "4",
            "2"
        ],
        "answer": 1
	},
	{
        "question": "How many gamepasses contain an exclusive vehicle?",
        "options": [
            "5",
            "3",
            "1",
            "2"
        ],
        "answer": 4
	},
	{
        "question": "How many laser gates are there in a completed base?",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "2",
            "5",
            "1"
        ],
        "answer": 1
	},
	{
        "question": "How many laser gates are there in a completed base?",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "2",
            "5",
            "1"
        ],
        "answer": 1
	},
	{
        "question": "Who is the creator of Military Warfare Tycoon?",
        "options": [
            "DevRolve",
            "forcetower",
            "asimo3089",
            "ObscureEntity"
        ],
        "answer": 2
	},
	{
        "question": "How much cash does the `helipad` cost?",
        "options": [
            "$25,000",
            "$100,000",
            "$35,000",
            "$50,000"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    }
]